http://www.sasol.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Home
Privacy policy
Privacy policy
Thank you for visiting our website. The protection of your personal data is important to us. Please take note of the following information pertaining to the collection and processing of data when visiting our website and contacting us.
Sasol collects, uses and allows access to your personal data in accordance with the laws pertaining to data privacy.
Personal data (“data”) refers to all information that can be used to determine who you are or data which can be traced back to you, for example your name, your e-mail address, IP address and telephone number.
Responsible body and Data Protection office
We, Sasol LTD, [Sasol Place, 50 Katherine Street, Sandton, South Africa, 2196] are the data controller and therefore responsible for data collection and processing on our websites. If you have any questions regarding our data processing, your rights or this privacy policy please contact our Data Protection office at privacy@sasol.com.
Data collected when you visit our website
Processed data collected:
If you visit our websites your browser automatically transmits the following data:
Date, time and duration of the time you have spent viewing a page
Name of your Internet Service Provider
The referring website
The IP (Internet Protocol) address of your device/ workstation / computer
Your internet browser type and version
The operating system of your device / workstation / computer
Purposes of data processing:
It is necessary to store data for a limited period of time to be able to deliver the website to your browser and to make sure that it works. With the help of this data we also obtain statistical information on how our websites are used. We also collect the data to prevent and track inadmissible access on our webservers and misuse of our websites as well as to secure our IT systems.
Legal basis:
We store the data based on legitimate interests. Our legitimate interest is to achieve the described purposes as outlined in this document.
Retention period and controlling options:
The data is deleted once it is no longer needed for the specific purposes outlined in this document.
Cookies
Processed data:
When you visit our website we collect data with the help of cookies. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your device. Cookies usually contain a cookie ID i.e. a unique identification feature that can be used to identify your browser.
Depending on the kind of the cookie, different data is collected and processed.
Our website uses Analysis cookies: With the help of these cookies we track your user behavior when you use our websites, e.g. which parts of the websites you use, how often you visit our websites. We use third party cookies only.
Purposes of data processing:
Analysis cookies help us generate statistics on how our websites are used, for instance the number of requests, duration of the visits, which parts of our websites are the most popular. This helps us to measure how effective our presence on the Internet is, to evaluate the activity on the websites and coordinate website content and functionality to improve the user experience.
Legal basis:
We process data based on legitimate interests. Our legitimate interest is to achieve the described purposes as outlined in this document. We process data based on your consent. You consent by clicking the button on our cookie banner.
Retention period and controlling options:
Some of the cookies are deleted after the browser is closed (session cookies), while others remain permanently on your device and allow us to recognise your browser (permanent cookies).
You are able to disable the storage of cookies or selectively accept certain cookies in your browser. Please use the Help functions of your browser to learn how to change these settings. Note this may result in limited functionality of our website.
Google Analytics
Processed data:
On our website we use "Google Analytics", a web analytics service of Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies on your device which assists in evaluating the use of our website (more information can be found here: https://policies.google.com/technologies/types)
We use the code "get. _anonymizeIP ();“ This results in Google shortening your IP address and allowing an anonymised evaluation. The reduction of IP addresses occurs within the EU or the European Economic Area. The IP address submitted by your browser as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with other Google data.
The data collected with the help of cookies is usually transferred to a Google server and stored there. Compliance with data protection standards and data rights is ensured by a certification under the EU-US privacy shield.
See the Google Privacy statement [https://policies.google.com/privacy] for more information.
Purposes of data processing:
On our behalf, Google uses the data collected through Google Analytics to evaluate the use of our website, to compile reports on the website activities and to provide further information related to the use of the website.
Legal basis:
Data is processed based on your consent. You consent by clicking the button on our cookie banner.
Retention period and controlling options:
Data is stored for a period of 14 months. You can prevent the storage of the Google Analytics cookies by a corresponding setting in your browser. This may restrict the functionality of our website.
You may also prevent the collection of data generated by cookies and use of the website (including your IP address) by Google and the processing of such data by Google by clicking the Opt-Out Button located on our cookie banner, this will place an opt-out-cookie on your browser. Learn more by clicking on the link below: https://policies.google.com/technologies/managing
Links to Sasol Social media pages
Sasol has links to their Social Media pages (Instagram, LinkedIn, Twitter and YouTube). If you visit these websites the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions of the specific website apply.
Data collected when you contact us
Processed data:
When you contact us via a contact form, via email or phone we process the personal data you communicate to us, e.g. your name, your email address and your request. The data will be stored in a Sasol repository. The data marked as mandatory has to be provided in order to action you request.
Purposes of data processing:
We use your data our in order to process and answer your request.
Legal basis:
We process data to take steps to action your request.
Retention period:
We store your data as long as it is necessary to fulfil the purposes mentioned above.
Your rights
Right to withdraw your consent:
You may withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data at any time by sending an email to privacy@sasol.com. Please note that the revocation does not affect the legality of the data processed thus far.
Right to object:
As far as the processing of personal data based on legitimate reasons you have the right to object on grounds relating to your particular situation. As far as we process personal data for direct marketing purposes you have the right to object at any time.
Other rights:
As a user you have certain rights. You can request information regarding the personal data processed by Sasol. Subject to legal requirements you can also submit a request to Sasol to amend incorrect data, or delete your personal data provided the request does not conflict with a statutory or contractual obligation to retain data.
Contact point for asserting your rights:
You can direct your queries to privacy@sasol.com.
Right to contact a supervisory authority:
You can file a claim with the respective data privacy supervisory authorities if you believe that our data processing does not meet the legal requirements or we did not grant your rights in the accordingly.
Last updated: May 2018
×
Stores
Total Stores
Division
Store Location
Address
Tel No
(021)6714778,
(031)4620540                     W\House                 (031) 469 9409
Maponya Shop 200 2127 Chris hani Road, klipspruit ext5 Soweto
(011) 933 1023
9
Relabelled
Umlazi
Shop 155 Umlazi Mega City 50 Griffiths Mxenge Highway Umlazi
Lifes on Kloof, 50 Kloof Street, Gardens ,Cape Town, shop G-15
(021) 422 1593            078 211 8051
2
BCWC
Canal Walk
Shop 619 Canal Walk , Century  BLVD, Century City , Cape Town 7441
(021) 551 2891
3
BCWC
Monte Casino
Shop 80B  Montecasino, No1 Monticasino Bouelvard  Fourways , 2191 Magents
(011) 465 0438
4
BCWC
Menlyn
Shop UF 42 & 43 cnr atterbury road & lois avenue , menlo park , Pretoria
Shop GF08, The Zone, Rosebank mall, Oxford Street, Johannesburg
Shop 21 Montecasino, No1 Monticasino Bouelvard  Fourways , 2191 Magents
(011) 465 6721                      074 669 6310                  073 804 4352              079 884 7607
3
Magents
Menlyn
MENLYN MALL , SHOP G190 CNR ATTERBURY ROAD & LOIS AVENUE,MENLO PARK,PRETORIA
(012) 348 4725            073 8677 468 - Sieya  , kiley , OUPA, Micheal
MENLYN MALL ,LF41A CNR ATTERBURY ROAD & LOIS AVENUE,MENLO PARK,PRETORIA
Vicky - 078 816 1921  land line -  012 348 4766
6
BCWC
Rosebank
Shop GF08, The Zone, Rosebank mall, Oxford Street, Johannesburg
Shop 21 Montecasino, No1 Monticasino Bouelvard  Fourways , 2191 Magents
(011) 465 6721                      074 669 6310                  073 804 4352              079 884 7607
3
Magents
Menlyn
MENLYN MALL , SHOP G190 CNR ATTERBURY ROAD & LOIS AVENUE,MENLO PARK,PRETORIA
(012) 348 4725            073 8677 468 - Sieya  , kiley , OUPA, Micheal
MENLYN MALL ,LF41A CNR ATTERBURY ROAD & LOIS AVENUE,MENLO PARK,PRETORIA
